Guide to the Puget Sound Advocates for Retirement Action Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Puget Sound Advocates for Retirement Action records
1984-2014
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
5803
Puget Sound Advocates for Retirement Action
4.15 cubic feet 4 boxes
Records of a retired citizens advocacy group
The Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans (PSARA) is a Seattle-based branch of the Alliance for Retired Americans. Founded in 1981, PSARA affiliated with the national Alliance of Retired Americans in 2001.
In 2002, the organization changed its name to the Puget Sound Council of Senior Citizens. The organization changed its name again in June of 2012 to the Puget Sound Advocates for Retirement Action and disaffiliated with the national Alliance of Retired Americans. The organization still works in close coordination with the Washington State Alliance of Retired Americans.
Organized into 2 accessions.
Accession No. 5803-001, Puget Sound Council of Senior Citizens records, 1984-2010
Accession No. 5803-002, Puget Sound Advocates for Retirement Action records, 1996-2014
Minutes, correspondence, agendas, newsletters, photographs, newspaper clippings, and petitions related to the organization, and issues of healthcare, housing, and income.
Records are stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
Open to all users.
Puget Sound Council of Senior Citizens$vArchives; Puget Sound Alliance of Retired Americans; Puget Sound Advocates for Retirement Action; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington)
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor Unions; Washington (State)
- Puget Sound Council of Senior Citizens records, 1984-2010; 5803-001; 3 cubic feet 3 boxes
  Minutes, correspondence, agendas, newsletters, photographs, newspaper clippings, and petitions related to the Puget Sound Council of Senior Citizens, also known as the Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans, and issues of healthcare, housing, and income.
  Records are stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
  Open to all users
  Donor: Maureen Bo, November 18, 2011.
- Puget Sound Advocates for Retirement Action records, 1996-2014; 5803-002; 1.15 cubic foot (1 box)
  Puget Sound Advocates for Retirement Action (PSARA) records from president Will Parry PSARA including executive board correspondence and meeting notes, materials from the King County Central Labor Council Housing Task Force, World Trade Organization notes and information, PSARA event and action announcements and materials, including Senior Lobby Day; and copies of "The Advocate" newsletter for years 2011 through 2014. Also includes a "Cover the Uninsured" banner.
  Open to all users.
  Maureen Bo, Puget Sound Alliance of Retired Americans, 2014-12-03
  - SERIES I: NEWSLETTERS, 2011-2014 (Box-folder 1/1-1/4)
    - The Retiree Advocate newsletter, 2011 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - The Retiree Advocate newsletter, 2012 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - The Retiree Advocate newsletter, 2013 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - The Retiree Advocate newsletter, 2014 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - SERIES II: CORRESPONDENCE AND NOTES, 1996-2006 (Box-folder 1/5-1/13)
    - Correspondence: Incoming (Will Parry), 1996-1998 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Correspondence: Outgoing (Will Parry), 1997 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Will Parry), 2002 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Will Parry), 2003 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Will Parry) (Part 1 of 2), 2004 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Will Parry) (Part 2 of 2), 2004 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Will Parry) (Part 1 of 2), 2005 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Will Parry) (Part 2 of 2), 2005 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Will Parry), 2006 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - SERIES III: EXECUTIVE BOARD MATERIALS, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 1/14-1/17)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 2005 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 2006 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 2007 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes, Agendas, and Correspondence, 2008 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - SERIES IV: ACTIVISM, 1997-2009 (Box-folder 1/18-1/22)
    - Political Action Forum, 2008 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Housing Task Force, 2007 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Senior Lobby Day, 2004-2009 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - World Trade Organization Notes and Information (Part 1 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - World Trade Organization Notes and Information (Part 2 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - SERIES V: EPHEMERA, Undated (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Red and black polyester banner "Cover the Uninsured - Let's Get America Covered - www.CoverTheUninsured.com", Undated (Box-folder 1/23 (oversized flat box))